http://www.malighting.de/privacy-policy/

DownloadsOnline ManualsTraining + SupportCommunityCompanyNewsLanguagesDeutschEnglish Service
Contact
MA Merchandising HomePrivacy PolicyBackPrivacy PolicyDachdeckerstraße 16 D – 97297 Waldbüttelbrunn, Germany Phone: +49 9 31 49 79 40 Fax: +49 9 31 49 79 42 80infonoSpam@malighting.com www.malighting.com Managing Directors: Michael Adenau, Gerhard Krude AG Würzburg HRB No. 4381 VAT No. DE 134 175 951 WEEE-Reg. No. DE 14150988An der Talle 24-28 D – 33102 Paderborn, Germany Phone: +49 52 51 68 88 65 10 Fax: +49 52 51 68 88 65 88salesnoSpam@malighting.comwww.malighting.com Managing Director: Stephan Saremba AG Paderborn HRB No. 3891 VAT No. DE 813 253 386Privacy PolicyYour privacy is important to us. The principles relating to processing of personal data in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) – transparency, lawfulness, purpose limitation, accuracy and data minimisation – are also the standards we set for ourselves when handling your data. We are strongly committed to living up to the trust you place in us. Consequently, we protect your personal data in particular against unauthorised access.The degree to which we collect, process and use your data depends on the form in which you make use of our offers. By visiting our website, you agree that we may collect, process, use and store your personal data to the extent specified below. We treat these data as confidential as a matter of course. The Privacy Policy is continuously revised and amended. The current version is dated December 2018. The controller is:MA Lighting International GmbHAn der Talle 24-28D-33102 Paderborn, DeutschlandPhone: +49 52 51 68 88 65 10Fax: +49 52 51 68 88 65 88sales@malighting.comwww.malighting.comManaging Director: Stephan SarembaLocal Court Paderborn Register No. HRB 3891VAT ID: DE 813 253 386 I. On overview of data protection1. General information The following information will provide you with an easy to navigate overview of what will happen with your personal data when you visit our website. The term “personal data” comprises all data that can be used to personally identify you. For detailed information on the subject of data protection, please refer to our Data Protection Declaration, which we have included below this document. 2. Data collection on our website Who is the responsible party for the collection of data on this website? The data on this website are processed by the operator of the website, whose contact information is available in section “Legal Notice“ of this website.How do we collect your data? We collect your data as a result of your sharing them with us. For example, this may involve data that you enter in a contact form.Our IT systems automatically record other data when you visit our website. These data are primarily technical information (e.g. web browser, operating system or time the site was accessed). This information is recorded automatically as soon as you access our website. Furthermore, data are processed by the plug-ins or programs we use.For what purposes do we use your data? Some of the data are collected to guarantee the error free provision of the website. Other data may be used to analyse your user behaviour.What rights do you have with regard to your personal data? You have the right to receive information about the source, recipient and purpose of your stored personal data at any time and free of charge.You also have the right to demand that your data are rectified, blocked or erased. Please do not hesitate to contact us at any time at the address given in section “Legal Notice“ on this website if you have questions about this or any other data protection related issues. Furthermore, You have the right to lodge a complaint with the responsible supervising authority. 3. Analysis-tools and third party tools When you visit our website, your browsing behaviour can be statistically evaluated. This is done primarily with cookies and so-called analysis programs. As a rule, the analysis of your browsing behaviour is conducted anonymously; i.e. the browsing behaviour cannot be traced back to you. You can object to this analysis or prevent it by not using certain tools. For details, please refer to our Privacy Policy under the heading "Third Party Modules and Analysis Tools".You do have the option to object to such an analysis. We will inform you on the objection options in this Data Protection Declaration. II. Detailed information1. General informationa) Personal dataPersonal data is information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person. This includes information about your identity such as your name, your e-mail address, or your postal address. Information that cannot be linked with your identity (such as statistical information used to count the number of website users) is not considered personal information.In principle, you can use our online service without disclosing your identity and without providing personal data. In that case we will only collect general information about your visit to our website. However, personal data are collected from you for some of the services offered. These data are  processed by us solely for the purpose of using this online service, in particular to provide the requested information.An automated decision-making process based on your personal data does not take place in connection with the use of our online service.b) Collection, processing and use of personal data when visiting our websiteAs the website operator, based on our legitimate interest (see Article 6 section lit. f. GDPR),  we collect data regarding access to this website and store such data as server log files on the website server. The following data are logged in this way: •    website visited •    file, date and time of access  •    volume of data sent (in bytes) •    report on successful access •    browser used (type and version) •    operating system used •    source/referrer from which you accessed the site (the website you visited before) •    IP-address usedThe server log files are erased regularly and automatically. The data are stored for statistical evaluations for the purpose of operation, optimisation and for security reasons, e.g. to clarify cases of misuse or malfunctions. If data must be collected for evidentiary purposes, they are excluded from erasure until matters have been finally resolved. These data are not merged with other data sources.Your personal data are transmitted in encrypted form over the Internet. We use SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption for the data transmission.c) Legal basis of data processingInsofar as we obtain your consent to processing of your personal data, Article 6 section 1 a) of the GDPR constitutes the legal basis for such data processing.Insofar as we process your personal data because processing is necessary under a legal obligation, Article 6, 1 lit. c) of the GDPR constitutes the legal basis for such data processing.Furthermore, Article 6 section 1 lit. f) of the GDPR may constitute the legal basis for data processing, if processing of your personal data is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by our company or by a third party, except where such interests are overridden by your interests or your fundamental rights and freedoms which require protection of personal data.Throughout this Privacy Policy, we refer to the legal basis on which we process your personal data.d) Use of cookiesWe use cookies so that we can provide you with individually optimized content. When you visit our website, you have the option of rejecting cookies. We recommend that you accept cookies, as otherwise the use of our website and our services is only available to a limited extent.Cookies are small text files that are stored on your system by your browser. The cookies remain stored until your browser is closed and can also automatically store certain information again even after you have left our website, for example if you call up our website again.(1) Our website uses the following types of cookies, the scope and function of which are explained below:      •    Transient cookies (see b)       •     persistent cookies (see c)(2)  Transient cookies are automatically deleted when you close your browser. These include in particular session cookies. They store a so-called session ID, which can be used to assign various requests from your browser to the respective session. This enables your computer to be recognised when you return to our website. The session cookies are deleted when you log out or close your browser.(3)  Persistent cookies remain on your system and enable us to recognize your browser the next time you visit. This allows us to take your saved settings and preferences into account during your next visit to our website. Persistent cookies will remain archived for a longer period of time. Check the cookie settings of your browser to find out about the storage period.(4) You can configure the settings of your browser according to your preferences, e.g., to make sure     that you are notified every time cookies are placed and to enable you to accept or reject cookies on a case-by-case basis or to exclude the acceptance of third party cookies or of all cookies. Please note that in that case you may not be able to use all functions of this website. Different browsers offer differing ways to configure cookie settings. This is described in the help menu of each browser which explains how you can change your cookie settings. Cookies are another way to serve user interests by ensuring that our services are as attractive, effective, smooth and user-friendly as possible. In the interest of a quick and easy handling of our website and our service offers, we have decided to also use cookies. The legal basis is Article 6 section 1 s. 1 lit. f) of the GDPR.e) Rights of the data subjectWe attach great importance to explaining the processing of your personal data as transparently as possible and to informing you about the rights to which you are entitled. If you would like more detailed information or wish to exercise your rights, you can contact us at any time so that we can respond to your request.You have extensive rights with regard to the processing of your personal data. First of all, you have an extensive right to information and can demand the rectification and/or erasure or blocking of your personal data if applicable. You can also demand a restriction of the processing and have a right of objection. With regard to the personal data you transmit to us, you also have the right to data portability.If you wish to exercise any of your rights and/or obtain further information, please contact us directly (see contact details above).If your personal data is processed on the basis of a balancing of interests in accordance with Article 6 section 1 lit. f), you may object to this data processing. Your objection will lead to a review and, if necessary, termination of the data processing. You will be informed of the result of the review and - if the data processing is to be continued after all - will receive more detailed information from us as to why the data processing is permissible.f) Protection of minorsChildren and young people under 18 years of age should not transfer any personal data to us without permission from their parents or guardians.g) LinksOn our homepage you will find links to offers of other operators. These links are clearly marked. We have no influence on the content of the linked pages or the compliance with the relevant data protection regulations. Please check which data protection provisions apply to the respective linked site. 2. Integration of third party providersa) Use of Google Web FontsThis page uses so-called web fonts provided by Google for the uniform display of fonts. The Google Fonts are installed locally. There is no connection to Google servers.b) Links to social mediaIn our online media you will find links to the social networks •    Facebook, •    Twitter, •    YouTube in the form of so-called "social plug-ins". You can recognize the links by the respective logos of the providers.We use the so-called two-click solution. This means that when you visit our site, no personal data is initially passed on to the providers of the plug-ins. You can recognize the provider of the plug-in by the mark on the box above their initial letter or by the logo. We offer you the possibility to communicate directly with the provider of the plug-in via the button. The plug-in provider will receive the information that you have called up the corresponding website of our online service only if you click on the marked field and thereby activate it. In addition, the data referred to above in this declaration will be transmitted. In the case of Facebook, for example, the IP address is made anonymous immediately after collection, according to information provided by the respective provider in Germany. Thus, by activating the plug-in, your personal data is transmitted to the respective plug-in provider and stored there (in the case of US providers in the USA). Since the plug-in provider collects data in particular via cookies, we recommend that you delete all cookies via your browser’s security settings before clicking on the grayed-out box.We have no influence on the collected data and data processing operations, nor are we aware of the full scope of data collection, the purposes of processing, the storage periods. We also do not have any information on the deletion of the collected data by the plug-in provider.The plug-in provider stores the data collected about you as user profiles and uses these for the purposes of advertising, market research and/or to better tailor their services to clients’ needs. Such an evaluation (that also includes users who are not logged in) is carried out in particular to display demand-oriented advertising and to inform other users of the social network about your activities on our website. You have the right to object to the creation of these user profiles. If you want to exercise this right, please contact the respective plug-in provider. By using plug-ins, we offer you the opportunity to interact with social networks and other users so that we can improve our service and make it more interesting for you as a user. The legal basis for the use of plug-ins is Article 6 section 1 s. 1 lit. f) of the GDPR. The data transfer takes place regardless of whether you have an account with the plug-in provider and are logged in there. If you are logged in with the plug-in provider, your data collected by us will be directly assigned to your existing account with the plug-in provider. If you press the activated button and, for example, link the page, the plug-in provider also stores this information in your user account and communicates it publicly to your contacts. We recommend that you log out regularly after using a social network, but especially before activating the button, as this allows you to avoid being assigned to your profile by the plug-in provider.You can obtain further information on the purpose and scope of data collection and processing by the plug-in provider in the following privacy policies of these providers. There you will also find further information on your rights in this matter and setting options to protect your privacy.If you activate a social plug-in, it remains active until you either deactivate it or delete your cookies.Further information on the purpose and scope of data collection and processing of the respective provider can be found in the corresponding privacy policy. There you will also find further information on your rights in this matter and setting options to protect your privacy:•    Facebook Inc., 1601 S California Ave, Palo Alto, California 94304, USA; www.facebook.com/policy.php; further information on data collection: www.facebook.com/help/186325668085084, www.facebook.com/about/privacy/your-info-on-other and www.facebook.com/about/privacy/your-info. Facebook consented to the EU-US-Privacy-Shield, www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-Frameworktwitter.com/de/privacy •    Twitter (Twitter Inc., 1355 Market Street, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA) – privacy policy: twitter.com/de/privacy, Opt-Out: twitter.com/personalization, Privacy Shield: www.privacyshield.gov/participant. •    Youtube (Google Ireland Limited (Register-No.: 368047),Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Irland) – privacy policy: policies.google.com/privacy 3. NewsletterWith your consent, you can subscribe to our newsletter, in which we inform you about our current interesting offers. The advertised goods and services are named in the declaration of consent.Following your future purchases of goods or services from us, we will send you e-mails with information on similar goods or services. These e-mails will not be sent unless an order is placed with us and are subject to the so-called double-opt-in-procedure. This means that we will not send you the information e-mails until you have confirmed your registration by sending us a confirmation e-mail via the link contained therein. You can request at any time to stop receiving such information e-mails from us. To do this, please send an e-mail with the subject "Unsubscribe" to infonoSpam@lightpower.de or to the contact data given in section “Legal Notice“. Alternatively, you can click on the link at the end of the information e-mail. No costs arise for you other than the transmission costs according to the basic rates.We use the so-called double opt-in-procedure to register for our newsletter. This means that after your registration we will send you an e-mail to the specified e-mail address in which we will ask you to confirm that you wish to receive the newsletter. If you do not confirm your registration within 24 hours, your information will be blocked and automatically deleted after one month. In addition, we save the IP addresses you use and the dates of registration and confirmation. The purpose of the procedure is to obtain proof of your registration and, if necessary, to clarify any possible misuse of your personal data.Your e-mail address is the only required information for sending the newsletter. Further, separately marked data are used to address you personally and are submitted on a voluntary basis. After receiving your confirmation we save your e-mail address for the purpose of sending you the newsletter. The legal basis is Article 6 section 1 s. 1 lit. a) of the GDPR.You can revoke your consent to the sending of the newsletter at any time and cancel your subscription to the newsletter. You can withdraw your consent by clicking on the link provided in every newsletter e-mail, (via this form on the website), by sending an e-mail to datenschutz@lightpower.de or by sending a message to the contact data given in the section “Legal Notice“.We would like to point out that we evaluate your user behaviour when sending the newsletter. The data are collected exclusively under a pseudonym, i.e. the IDs are not linked to your other personal data and there is no possibility of direct personal identification.You may object to this tracking at any time by clicking on the separate link provided in every e-mail or by informing us through another communication channel. The information is stored for as long as you subscribe to the newsletter. If you unsubscribe, the data we store are strictly statistical and anonymous.You can cancel your subscription to our newsletter, i.e. revoke your consent to receive it, at any time by clicking on the respective link provided in every newsletter. You can also revoke your consent by sending us a short message. For this purpose, please use the contact data stated above.Based on our legitimate interests, we may store the removed e-mail address for up to three years before it is deleted, so that we are able to provide proof of a previously given consent. In this context, the e-mail address is solely stored for the purpose of defence against possible claims. 4. Contact formThere are a number of ways in which you can contact us, including using the contact form on our website.If you wish to use the contact form of our online service, we record the personal data you provide in the contact form, in particular•    first name, •    surname, •    company name, •    postal address, •    telephone number, •    e-mail address, •    IP-address and •    date and time of the inquiry.We process the data transmitted through the contact form exclusively for the purpose of answering your inquiry or request and any follow-up questions that may occur.You decide what information you send us through the contact form. The legal basis for the processing of your data is your consent according to Article 6 section 1 lit. a) of the GDPR.Following the handling of the matter, we initially store the data in case there are any follow-up queries. A deletion of the data can be requested at any time. Otherwise, the data are erased after the matter has been fully dealt with; statutory retention obligations remain unaffected in each case. 5. Request per e-mail, telephone or telefaxIf you contact us per e-mail, telephone or telefax, your request including the provided personal data (e-mail address, inquiry) will be stored and processed for the purpose of responding to your request. These data will not be disclosed to third parties without your consent. Basis for processing is Article 6 section 1 lit. b of the GDPR if the purpose of your request relates to the conclusion of a contract or is necessary for the implementation of pre-contractual measures. In all other cases, the processing is based on your consent (Article 6 section 1 lit. a GDPR) and / or our legitimate interests (Article 6 section 1 lit. f GDPR) since we have a legitimate interest in the effective processing of requests addressed to us. The data we receive from you per contact request remain with us until you request us to delete them, revoke your consent to the storage or the purpose for the data storage no longer exists (e.g. after completion of your request). Mandatory statutory provisions – in particular statutory retention periods – remain unaffected. 6.  Data processing (customer and contractural data)We collect, process and use personal data only to the extent necessary for the establishment, content and structure or modification of the legal relationship (inventory data). The basis for this is Article 6 section 1 lit. b GDPR which permits the processing of data relating to the conclusion of a contract or pre-contractual measures. We collect, process and use personal data concerning the use of our website (usage data) only to the extent that this is necessary to make it possible for users to utilize the service or for invoicing purposes. The collected customer data are erased upon completion of the order or the termination of the business relationship. Statutory retention periods remain unaffected. 7.  Job applicationsYou have the opportunity to submit job applications to us (e.g. by e-mail, by post). Below, you will find information on the scope, purpose and use of the personal data collected from you in connection with the application process. We assure you that the collection, processing and use of your data will occur in compliance with the applicable data privacy rights and all other statutory provisions and that your data will be treated as strictly confidential.Scope and purpose of data collectionIf you submit a job application to us, we will process your affiliated personal data (e.g. contact and communication data, application documents, notes taken during job interviews, etc.), if they are required to make a decision concerning the establishment of an employment relationship. The legal grounds for this are  § 26 GDPR-new according to German Law (Negotiation of an Employment Relationship), Article 6 section 1 lit. b GDPR (General Contract Negotiations) and – provided you have given us your consent –  Article 6, lit. a GDPR. You may revoke the consent given at any time. Within our company, your personal data will be disclosed exclusively to individuals who are involved in the processing of your job application.If the job application is successful, the data you have submitted will be stored in our data processing systems on the basis of § 26 GDPR-new and Article 6 section 1 lit. b GDPR for the purpose of carrying out the employment relationship.Data retention period If we should not be able to offer you a position, if you decline a job offer, withdraw your application, revoke your consent to the processing of your data or ask us to delete your data, we will store your transferred data, incl. any physically submitted application documents for a maximum of  6 months after the conclusion of the application process (retention period) to enable us to retrace the details of the application process in the event of any discrepancies (Article 6 section 1 lit. f GDPR).YOU HAVE THE OPTION TO OBJECT TO THIS STORAGE OF YOUR DATA IF YOU HAVE LEGITIMATE INTERESTS TO DO SO THAT OUTWEIGH OUR INTERESTS.Once the retention period has expired, the data will be deleted unless there is a statutory retention obligation or any other legal ground that requires continuation of data storage. If it is evident that the storage of your data will be necessary after the expiration of the retention period (e.g. due to an anticipated or pending legal dispute), deletion will only take place when the data has become redundant. Other statutory storage obligations remain unaffected. 8. Use of our e-learning platformIf you wish to use our e-learning portal (https://elearning.malighting.com/), you can register by entering your e-mail address and a password of your choice. There is no obligation to use your real name, a pseudonymous use is possible. We use the so-called double opt-in procedure for registration, i.e. your registration is not completed until you have clicked on the link in the confirmation e-mail sent to you for this purpose. If your confirmation is not received within [24 hours], your registration will automatically be deleted from our database. The above mentioned data are obligatory; any additional information can be provided voluntarily on our platform.If you use our platform, we store the required data for contract performance until you permanently delete your access. Furthermore, we store the voluntary data provided by you for the duration of your use of the platform, unless you delete them beforehand. You can manage and change all data in the secure customer area. The legal basis is Article 6 section 1 s. 1 lit. f of the GDPR.An encrypted connection per TLS technolgy prevents unauthorised third parties from accessing your personal details, in particular financial data.  9. Use of Google AnalyticsThis website uses functions of the web analysis service Google Analytics. The provider is Google Ireland Limited (“Google”), Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Irland. Google Analytics uses so-called “cookies“ that facilitate an analysis of your user behaviour on the website. The information generated by the cookies is usually transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there. However, if IP anonymisation is activated on this website, your IP address will be shortened by Google within member states of the European Union or in other signatory states to the Agreement on the European Economic Area prior to transmission. Only in exceptional cases is the full IP address transmitted to a Google server in the USA and shortened there. On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, to compile reports on website activity and to provide the website operator with other services relating to website activity and Internet usage. The IP address transmitted by your browser as part of Google Analytics is not merged with other data from Google.You can prevent the storage of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. You can also prevent Google from collecting the data generated by the cookie that relate to your use of the website (including your IP address) and from processing this data by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available under the following link: //http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en.As an alternative to the browser plug-in,  you can click on the following link to prevent Google Analytics from collecting  data on this website in the future: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en An opt-out cookie will be placed on your device. If you delete your cookies, you have to click on the link again.For further information, please see http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en or http://www.google.com/intl/de/analytics/privacyoverview.html (general information about Google Analytics and data privacy).Objection to data collection You can prevent Google Analytics from collecting your data by clicking on the following link: Adjust cookie settings.  III. Privacy policy for the facebook page (fanpage)We use Facebook for the operation of a so-called fanpage. Here we present useful information about our company and our products to interested facebook users. We also offer users the opportunity to contact us through this medium and leave comments.As the operator of a fanpage, we can obtain anonymous statistical data regarding the users of these pages by means of the Facebook Insight function, which Facebook makes available free of charge as an indispensable part of the user agreement. This data is collected by means of so-called cookies, which contain a unique user code that is active for two years and stores Facebook on the hard disk of the computer or another data carrier of the fan page visitors. The user code, which can be linked to the login data of users who are registered with Facebook, is collected and processed when the fan page is accessed.Thus, by using our fan page, your personal data are transmitted to Facebook and stored there (at US providers in the USA). We have no influence on the collected data and data processing operations, nor are we aware of the full scope of data collection, the purposes of processing, the storage periods. We also do not have any information on the deletion of the collected data by Facebook.Facebook stores the data collected about you as user profiles and uses these for the purposes of advertising, market research and/or to better tailor their services to clients’ needs. Such an evaluation (that also includes users who are not logged in) is carried out in particular to display demand-oriented advertising and to inform other users of the social network about your activities on our website. You have the right to object to the creation of these user profiles. If you want to exercise this right, please contact Facebook. By using Facebook, we offer you the opportunity to interact with social networks and other users so that we can improve our service and make it more interesting for you as a user. The legal basis for the use of plug-ins is Article 6 section 1 s. 1 lit. f) of the GDPR.Further information on the purpose and scope of data collection and processing of the respective provider can be found in the corresponding privacy policy. There you will also find further information on your rights in this matter and setting options to protect your privacy: •    Facebook Inc., 1601 S California Ave, Palo Alto, California 94304, USA; www.facebook.com/policy.php; further information on data collection: www.facebook.com/help/186325668085084, www.facebook.com/about/privacy/your-info-on-other and www.facebook.com/about/privacy/your-info. Facebook consented to the EU-US-Privacy-Shield, https://www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-Framework. In accordance with Article 26 GDPR, we have concluded an agreement with Facebook regarding the responsibility for data usage. The principal and primary responsibility rests with Facebook.  https://www.facebook.com/legal/terms/page_controller_addendum
Pursuant to this agreement, we hereby inform you that•     the legal basis for the use of the fanpage is our interest in the interaction with our customers and      an improved service according to Article 6 section 1 lit f) GDPR (see above) and •     that you can exercise your rights as a data subject directly against Facebook or communicate          them to the entity identified in this privacy policy. We will then forward these concerns to      Facebook. In addition, we refer to the explanations in this privacy policy.   IV. Data protection officerIf you have any questions regarding the collection, processing or use of your personal data that this privacy policy could not answer, or regarding the rectification or deletion of your data, please contact the responsible party. We have appointed a data protection officer for our company.MA Lighting International GmbH Abteilung Datenschutz An der Talle 24-28 D-33102 PaderbornE-Mail: datenschutznoSpam@malighting.com V. Right to lodge a complaintYou have the right to report suspected violations of the provisions of data protection law and to complain to the responsible supervisory authority. You can address the complaint to:Landesbeauftragte für Datenschutz und Informationsfreiheit Nordrhein-Westfalen (State Commissioner for Data Protection and Freedom of Information North Rhine-Westphalia) Postfach 20 04 44 40102 Düsseldorf Tel.: 0211/38424-0 Fax: 0211/38424-10 E-Mail: poststelle@ldi.nrw.deYou can also, especially if you are not a German citizen, either address the responsible authority of your member state or contact: Die Bundesbeauftragte für den Datenschutz und die Informationsfreiheit (Federal Commissioner for Data Protection and Freedom of Information) Husarenstr. 30 53117 Bonn Telefon: +49 (0)228 997799-0 Fax: +49 (0)228 997799-5550 redaktion@bfdi.bund.de
